Jhal
[Music]
I am Suresh, a scientist, Dr. Jhal, today in this video we will look at
important detox at this level
you have an option and that is with Bigg Boss and
your future end option. If you don't
want to do this then watch this video, as you
can see today and subscribe and see
your solid, then let's
see which chart
toxins are there, let's introduce ourselves, the
first square in our list is
HDFC Life Insurance Company,
after its results today, in this we are
extra bullish on 10, if you have this, then
you have to click on your and 56001,
you have to click on the extra stroke or
that too on it for a second, let's
talk about this and talk about other stocks in
which after the research, we can
see a decline in the future also,
here we are talking about Mahindra &
Mahindra sell stop today we have 8.75 questions
together and we get to see and
because the stock is dedicated, then in this
tomorrow also you will have one seal and in this, plus
you will have one seal under the soil
and you  60 and target, then you
must put your stop loss here, which is the third one, in that today
due to short coming, a little bit of upset is
seen, but because the
Government of India has clarified Tejas
Express by looking at the temperature lipstick points, then
after the market opens tomorrow, you should
simultaneously take another episode of ICC stock here and 1000 and
because this is quite high, then you should take this
thing here with the Authority of India, that is, India, if
you stay
here on a Prabhu, then you
can write this in a research and that too,
twists will come within 15 minutes and
now you must achieve the target,
if you talk about soil and above, there is
a continuation in soil here, but if
you do not take it above 1000 in a hurry from yesterday,
if it breaks the dip here till 300,
that intestine, if it
breaks the dip here at 1000 due to rotting hormones, then you should
take a hot trend forward on this side, in the traffic jam
center you will see Nifty floating below 2018  You can get a
chance to take a shot on the break of
2000 contact and you can take it
further in this chapter note or opposition after this when it is
seen then you will see some consolidation
and bye-bye till 10 2012 that
when it is 3200 above it left from that
3200 3200 Jaipur contact, you can take it in
chapter note or pet for this you will have to follow want to
minute only then you will be able to
do Nifty and brinjal as soon as possible along with this video if you like it
then do like it and subscribe to the channel
and if something is on you then
you must do it so that you can help in
trading by providing membership mode here
well we will give you Singh National Plate here
so see you in the
next video in the next video
[music]